Jeff Brozena, Teacher, Operator, Analyst

jeff@brozena.net	+1	(570)	335-8269
------------------	----	-------	----------

SI	IN	ΛN	1	ΔR	v

An operator-teacher with broad and deep experience at one of the country's largest and most respected privately-held Medicaid pediatric dental groups. I was entrusted to set strategic direction, improve core business processes and lead complex change shortly before a cross-generational ownership transfer was expected. My impact at this group was described positively as "like a crater" by its ownership.

EXPERIENCE

Penn State University, Research Support

Sep 2019 — present

- o College of Information Sciences & Technology, Wellbeing and Health Innovation Lab
- Working to develop a conceptual and technical framework to detect mental health states using multi-modal data streams reflecting online activities.

The Smilist Management, Manager of Optimization

Feb 2018 — Aug 2018

Smiles 4 Keeps Pediatric Dentistry, Practice Operations

Aug 2012 - Nov 2017

- Responsible for a complete digital transformation in the midst of a generational ownership transfer, resulting in accurate third-party valuation of business.
- Spoke publicly at American Academy of Pediatric Dentistry, Pennsylvania Academy of Pediatric Dentistry on the subjects of digitization and compliant record-keeping.

Bedrock Technology, Technician

Jan 2012 — Aug 2012

Appek Mobile Apps, Project Manager

May 2011 — Dec 2012

Penn State University, Research Assistant

May 2009 — Jan 2010

 ${\color{gray} \bullet} \ \, \text{College of Information Sciences \& Technology, Human-Computer Interaction Lab}$

Penn State University, Software Trainer

Aug 2007 — Dec 2009

• Promoted to supervisory position in June, 2009.

AWARDS

Rock Ethics Stand Up Award, Penn State University

Apr 2011

Emerging Scholars Fellowship, Active Minds, Inc.

Jan 2011

EDUCATION

Pennsylvania State University

Aug 2008 — Dec 2019

BS - Information Sciences & Technology

SKILLS

Leadership: Public speaking, Systems thinking, Whole systems management, Written & verbal clarity, Motivational interviewing, Situational leadership

Digital transformation: Software training, Transformational change, Change management, Strategic planning, Business analysis

Healthcare information technology (HIT): HIPAA compliance, Electronic data interchange (EDI), Electronic medical record (EMR), Analytics, SQL, Product management, Systems integration, Software integration, Electronic remittance advice (ERA), Clinical decision support

Program management: Process improvement, Project management, Process optimization, Process management, Lean Six Sigma, Kaizen

.....